
<DOCUMENT>
<TYPE>XML
<SEQUENCE>98
<FILENAME>R24.xml
<DESCRIPTION>IDEA: Commitments and Contingencies
<TEXT>
<XBRL>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<InstanceReport xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Version>2.2.0.7</Version>
  <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
  <ReportName>Commitments and Contingencies</ReportName>
  <ReportLongName>11701 - Disclosure - Commitments and Contingencies</ReportLongName>
  <DisplayLabelColumn>true</DisplayLabelColumn>
  <ShowElementNames>false</ShowElementNames>
  <RoundingOption />
  <HasEmbeddedReports>false</HasEmbeddedReports>
  <Columns>
    <Column>
      <LabelColumn>false</LabelColumn>
      <Id>1</Id>
      <Labels>
        <Label Id="1" Label="12 Months Ended" />
        <Label Id="2" Label="Sep. 30, 2010" />
      </Labels>
      <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
      <FootnoteIndexer />
      <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
      <hasScenarios>false</hasScenarios>
      <Segments />
      <Scenarios />
      <Units>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>Unit1</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Standard</UnitType>
          <StandardMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/iso4217</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>USD</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>iso4217</MeasureNamespace>
          </StandardMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>Unit13</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Standard</UnitType>
          <StandardMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>pure</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>xbrli</MeasureNamespace>
          </StandardMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>Unit15</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Standard</UnitType>
          <StandardMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>shares</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>xbrli</MeasureNamespace>
          </StandardMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>Unit12</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Divide</UnitType>
          <NumeratorMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/iso4217</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>USD</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>iso4217</MeasureNamespace>
          </NumeratorMeasure>
          <DenominatorMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>shares</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>xbrli</MeasureNamespace>
          </DenominatorMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
      </Units>
      <CurrencySymbol>$</CurrencySymbol>
    </Column>
  </Columns>
  <Rows>
    <Row>
      <Id>2</Id>
      <Label>Commitments and Contingencies</Label>
      <Level>0</Level>
      <ElementName>apd_CommitmentsAndContingenciesAbstract</ElementName>
      <ElementPrefix>apd</ElementPrefix>
      <IsBaseElement>false</IsBaseElement>
      <BalanceType>na</BalanceType>
      <PeriodType>duration</PeriodType>
      <ShortDefinition>No definition available.</ShortDefinition>
      <IsReportTitle>false</IsReportTitle>
      <IsSegmentTitle>false</IsSegmentTitle>
      <IsSubReportEnd>false</IsSubReportEnd>
      <IsCalendarTitle>false</IsCalendarTitle>
      <IsTuple>false</IsTuple>
      <IsAbstractGroupTitle>true</IsAbstractGroupTitle>
      <IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>false</IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>
      <IsEquityAdjustmentRow>false</IsEquityAdjustmentRow>
      <IsBeginningBalance>false</IsBeginningBalance>
      <IsEndingBalance>false</IsEndingBalance>
      <IsReverseSign>false</IsReverseSign>
      <PreferredLabelRole />
      <IsEPS>false</IsEPS>
      <FootnoteIndexer />
      <Cells>
        <Cell>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <ShowCurrencySymbol>false</ShowCurrencySymbol>
          <IsNumeric>false</IsNumeric>
          <IsRatio>false</IsRatio>
          <DisplayZeroAsNone>false</DisplayZeroAsNone>
          <NumericAmount>0</NumericAmount>
          <RoundedNumericAmount>0</RoundedNumericAmount>
          <NonNumbericText />
          <NonNumericTextHeader />
          <FootnoteIndexer />
          <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
          <hasScenarios>false</hasScenarios>
          <DisplayDateInUSFormat>false</DisplayDateInUSFormat>
        </Cell>
      </Cells>
      <OriginalInstanceReportColumns />
      <ElementDataType>xbrli:stringItemType</ElementDataType>
      <SimpleDataType>string</SimpleDataType>
      <ElementDefenition>No definition available.</ElementDefenition>
      <IsTotalLabel>false</IsTotalLabel>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <Id>3</Id>
      <Label>Commitments and Contingencies</Label>
      <Level>1</Level>
      <ElementName>us-gaap_CommitmentsAndContingenciesDisclosureTextBlock</ElementName>
      <ElementPrefix>us-gaap</ElementPrefix>
      <IsBaseElement>true</IsBaseElement>
      <BalanceType>na</BalanceType>
      <PeriodType>duration</PeriodType>
      <ShortDefinition>No definition available.</ShortDefinition>
      <IsReportTitle>false</IsReportTitle>
      <IsSegmentTitle>false</IsSegmentTitle>
      <IsSubReportEnd>false</IsSubReportEnd>
      <IsCalendarTitle>false</IsCalendarTitle>
      <IsTuple>false</IsTuple>
      <IsAbstractGroupTitle>false</IsAbstractGroupTitle>
      <IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>false</IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>
      <IsEquityAdjustmentRow>false</IsEquityAdjustmentRow>
      <IsBeginningBalance>false</IsBeginningBalance>
      <IsEndingBalance>false</IsEndingBalance>
      <IsReverseSign>false</IsReverseSign>
      <PreferredLabelRole>verboselabel</PreferredLabelRole>
      <IsEPS>false</IsEPS>
      <FootnoteIndexer />
      <Cells>
        <Cell>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <ShowCurrencySymbol>false</ShowCurrencySymbol>
          <IsNumeric>false</IsNumeric>
          <IsRatio>false</IsRatio>
          <DisplayZeroAsNone>false</DisplayZeroAsNone>
          <NumericAmount>0</NumericAmount>
          <RoundedNumericAmount>0</RoundedNumericAmount>
          <NonNumbericText>&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a name="tx17525_38"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;17.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Commitments and Contingencies &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Litigation &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company is involved in various legal proceedings, including competition, environmental, health, safety, product liability, and insurance matters. In September 2010, the Brazilian Administrative Council for Economic Defense (CADE) issued a decision against the Company's Brazilian subsidiary, Air Products Brasil Ltda., and several other Brazilian industrial gas companies for alleged anticompetitive activities. CADE imposed a civil fine of R$&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;179.2&lt;/font&gt; on Air Products Brasil Ltda. This fine was based on a recommendation by a unit of the Brazilian Ministry of Justice whose investigation began in 2003 alleging violation of competition laws with respect to the sale of industrial and medical gases. The fines are based on a percentage of the Company's total revenue in Brazil in 2003. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company has denied the allegations made by the authorities and filed an appeal in October 2010 to the Brazilian courts. Certain of the Company's defenses, if successful, could result in the matter being dismissed with no fine against the Company. The Company, with advice of its outside legal counsel, has assessed the status of this matter and has concluded that although an adverse final judgment after exhausting all appeals is reasonably possible, such a judgment is not probable. As a result, no provision has been made in the consolidated financial statements. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company is required to provide security in order to suspend execution of the judgment during the appeal process, during which time interest will accrue on the fine. The security could be in the form of a bank guarantee or in other forms which the courts deem acceptable. The security is only collectible by the courts in the event the Company is not successful in its appeal and does not timely pay the fine. The form of security to be provided by the Company has not been finally determined. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;While the Company does not expect that any sums it may have to pay in connection with this or any other legal proceeding would have a materially adverse effect on its consolidated financial position or net cash flows, a future charge for regulatory fines or damage awards could have a significant impact on the Company's net income in the period in which it is recorded. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environmental&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In the normal course of business, the Company is involved in legal proceedings under the federal Superfund law, similar state environmental laws, and RCRA relating to the designation of certain sites for investigation or remediation. Presently, there are approximately&amp;nbsp;&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;30&lt;/font&gt; sites on which a final settlement has not been reached where the Company, along with others, has been designated a potentially responsible party by the Environmental Protection Agency or is otherwise engaged in investigation or remediation. In addition, the Company is also involved in cleanup activities at certain of its current and former manufacturing sites. The Company continually monitors these sites for which it has environmental exposure. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;Accruals for environmental loss contingencies are recorded when it is probable that a liability has been incurred and the amount of loss can be reasonably estimated consistent with the policy set forth in Note 1, Major Accounting Policies. The consolidated balance sheets at 30 September&amp;nbsp;2010 and 2009 included an accrual of $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;87.0&lt;/font&gt; and $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;95.0&lt;/font&gt;, respectively, primarily as part of other noncurrent liabilities. The environmental liabilities will be paid over a period of up to&amp;nbsp;&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;30&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;years. The Company estimates the exposure for environmental loss contingencies to range from $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;87&lt;/font&gt; to a reasonably possible upper exposure of $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;101&lt;/font&gt; as of 30 September&amp;nbsp;2010. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;Actual costs to be incurred at identified sites in future periods may vary from the estimates, given inherent uncertainties in evaluating environmental exposures. Using reasonably possible alternative assumptions of the exposure level could result in an increase to the environmental accrual. Due to the inherent uncertainties related to environmental exposures, a significant increase to the reasonably possible upper exposure level could occur if a new site is designated, the scope of remediation is increased, a different remediation alternative is identified, or a significant increase in the Company's proportionate share occurs. The Company does not expect that any sum it may have to pay in connection with environmental matters in excess of the amounts recorded or disclosed above would have a material adverse impact on its financial position or results of operations in any one year. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;P&lt;small&gt;ACE&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;At 30&amp;nbsp;September&amp;nbsp;2010, $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;36.5&lt;/font&gt; of the environmental accrual was related to the Pace facility. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In 2006, the Company sold its Amines business, which included operations at Pace, Florida and recognized a liability for retained environmental obligations associated with remediation activities at Pace. The Company is required by the Florida Department of Environmental Protection (FDEP)&amp;nbsp;and the United States Environmental Protection Agency (USEPA)&amp;nbsp;to continue its remediation efforts. The Company estimated that it would take about&amp;nbsp;&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;20&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;years to complete the groundwater remediation, and the costs through completion were estimated to range from $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;42&lt;/font&gt; to $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;50&lt;/font&gt;. As no amount within the range was a better estimate than another, the Company recognized a pretax expense in fiscal 2006 of $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;42.0&lt;/font&gt; as a component of income from discontinued operation
s and recorded an environmental accrual of $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;42.0&lt;/font&gt; in continuing operations on the consolidated balance sheets. There has been no change to the estimated exposure range related to the Pace facility. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company has implemented many of the remedial corrective measures at the Pace, Florida facility required under 1995 Consent Orders issued by the FDEP and the USEPA. Contaminated soils have been bioremediated, and the treated soils have been secured in a lined on-site disposal cell. Several groundwater recovery systems have been installed to contain and remove contamination from groundwater. The Company completed an extensive assessment of the site to determine how well existing measures are working, what additional corrective measures may be needed, and whether newer remediation technologies that were not available in the 1990s might be suitable to more quickly and effectively remove groundwater contaminants. Based on assessment results, &lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;the Company completed a focused feasibility study that identified new and alternative approaches which should mor
e effectively remove contaminants and achieve the targeted remediation goals. The Company is reviewing the new approaches with the FDEP. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;P&lt;small&gt;IEDMONT&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;At 30&amp;nbsp;September&amp;nbsp;2010, $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;21.5&lt;/font&gt; of the environmental accrual was related to the Piedmont site. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;On 30 June&amp;nbsp;2008, the Company sold its Elkton, Maryland and Piedmont, South Carolina production facilities and the related North American atmospheric emulsions and global pressure sensitive adhesives businesses. In connection with the sale, the Company recognized a liability for retained environmental obligations associated with remediation activities at the Piedmont site. This site is under active remediation for contamination caused by an insolvent prior owner. The sale of the site triggered expense recognition. Prior to the sale, remediation costs had been capitalized since they improved the property as compared to its condition when originally acquired. The Company is required by the South Carolina Department of Health and Environmental Control to address both contaminated soil and groundwater. Numerous areas of soil contamination have been addressed, and contaminated groundwater is being recovered a
nd treated. The Company estimated that it would take until 2015 to complete source area remediation and another&amp;nbsp;&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;15&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;years thereafter to complete groundwater recovery, with costs through completion estimated to be $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;24.0&lt;/font&gt;. The Company recognized a pretax expense in 2008 of $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;24.0&lt;/font&gt; as a component of income from discontinued operations and recorded an environmental liability of $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;24.0&lt;/font&gt; in continuing operations on the consolidated balance sheets. There has been no change to the estimated exposure. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;P&lt;small&gt;AULSBORO&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;At 30&amp;nbsp;September&amp;nbsp;2010, $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;14.0&lt;/font&gt; of the environmental accrual was related to the Paulsboro site. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;During the first quarter of 2009, management committed to a plan to sell the production facility in Paulsboro, New Jersey and recognized a $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;16.0&lt;/font&gt; environmental liability associated with this site. In December 2009, the Company completed the sale of this facility. The Company is required by the New Jersey state law to investigate and, if contaminated, remediate a site upon its sale. The Company estimates that it will take at least several years to complete the investigation/remediation efforts at this site. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guarantees and Warranties &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company is a party to certain guarantee agreements, including debt guarantees of equity affiliates and equity support agreements. These guarantees are contingent commitments that are related to activities of the Company's primary businesses. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company has guaranteed repayment of some additional borrowings of certain unconsolidated equity affiliates. At 30&amp;nbsp;September&amp;nbsp;2010, these guarantees have terms in the range of two to eight years, with maximum potential payments of $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;28.7&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company has entered into an equity support agreement and operations guarantee related to an air separation facility constructed in Trinidad for a venture in which the Company owns &lt;font class="_mt"&gt;50&lt;/font&gt;%. At 30&amp;nbsp;September&amp;nbsp;2010, maximum potential payments under joint and several guarantees were $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;68.0&lt;/font&gt;. Exposures under the guarantee decline over time and are completely extinguished by &lt;font class="_mt"&gt;2024&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;To date, no equity contributions or payments have been required since the inception of these guarantees. The fair value of the above guarantees is not material. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company, in the normal course of business operations, has issued product warranties in its Equipment business. Also, contracts often contain standard terms and conditions which typically include a warranty and indemnification to the buyer that the goods and services purchased do not infringe on third-party intellectual property rights. The provision for estimated future costs relating to warranties is not material to the consolidated financial statements. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company does not expect that any sum it may have to pay in connection with guarantees and warranties will have a materially adverse effect on its consolidated financial condition, liquidity, or results of operations. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Put Option Agreements &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company has entered into put option agreements with certain affiliated companies as discussed below. The Company accounts for the put options as contingent liabilities to purchase an asset. Since the inception of these agreements and through 30&amp;nbsp;September&amp;nbsp;2010, the Company determined that it was not certain that these options would be exercised by the other shareholders. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt; &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In 2002, the Company entered into a put option agreement as part of the purchase of an additional interest in San Fu Gas Company, Ltd., renamed Air Products San Fu Company, Ltd. (San Fu), an industrial gas company in Taiwan. Currently, the Company has an ownership interest of &lt;font class="_mt"&gt;74&lt;/font&gt;% in San Fu. Put options were issued which give other shareholders the right to sell San Fu stock to the Company at market price when exercised. The options are effective through January&amp;nbsp;2015 and allow for the sale of all stock owned by other shareholders to the Company. The estimated U.S. dollar price of purchasing the stock owned by other shareholders based on the exchange rate at 30&amp;nbsp;September&amp;nbsp;2010 would be approximately $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;240&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In 1999, the Company made an investment in INOX, an Indian industrial gases company. As part of that transaction, put options were issued which gave the other (joint &lt;font class="_mt"&gt;50&lt;/font&gt;%) shareholders the right to require the Company to purchase their shares (approximately&amp;nbsp;&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;5.1&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;million) of INOX (renamed INOXAP) at a predefined price. The other shareholders may give notice to exercise the put option between October and December&amp;nbsp;2010. The option, if exercised, would be effective on 31&amp;nbsp;July 2011. The option may also be exercised within six months of the death or permanent incapacity of the current Managing Director of INOXAP. The option price is based on a multiple of earnings formula, but not less than&amp;nbsp;&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;630&lt;/font&gt; Rupees per share. The U.S. dollar price of purchasing all&amp;nbsp;&lt;font c
lass="_mt"&gt;5.1&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;million shares based on the multiple of earnings formula at the 30&amp;nbsp;September 2010 exchange rate would be approximately $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;190&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Purchase Obligations &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The Company is obligated to make future payments under unconditional purchase obligations as summarized below: &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px; font-size: 6px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="98%" align="center"&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td width="90%"&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" width="5%"&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr bgcolor="#cceeff"&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
&lt;p style="text-indent: -1em; margin-left: 1em;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;2011&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font class="_mt" size="1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" align="right"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;$482&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" nowrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
&lt;p style="text-indent: -1em; margin-left: 1em;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;2012&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font class="_mt" size="1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" align="right"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;100&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" nowrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr bgcolor="#cceeff"&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
&lt;p style="text-indent: -1em; margin-left: 1em;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;2013&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font class="_mt" size="1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" align="right"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;103&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" nowrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
&lt;p style="text-indent: -1em; margin-left: 1em;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;2014&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font class="_mt" size="1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" align="right"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;112&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" nowrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr bgcolor="#cceeff"&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
&lt;p style="text-indent: -1em; margin-left: 1em;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;2015&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font class="_mt" size="1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" align="right"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;118&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td valign="bottom" nowrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="top"&gt;
&lt;p style="text-indent: -1em; margin-left: 1em;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;Thereafter&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font class="_mt" size="1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="bottom" align="right"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;551&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="bottom" nowrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr bgcolor="#cceeff"&gt;&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="top"&gt;
&lt;p style="text-indent: -1em; margin-left: 1em;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Total&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font class="_mt" size="1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="bottom"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="bottom" align="right"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;$1,466&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="border-bottom: #000000 1px solid;" valign="bottom" nowrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;Most of the Company's long-term unconditional purchase obligations relate to feedstock supply for numerous HyCO (hydrogen, carbon monoxide, and syngas) facilities. The price of feedstock supply is principally related to the price of natural gas. However, long-term take-or-pay sales contracts to HyCO customers are generally matched to the term of the feedstock supply obligations and provide recovery of price increases in the feedstock supply. Due to the matching of most feedstock supply obligations to customer sales contracts, the Company does not believe these purchase obligations would have a material effect on its financial condition or results of operations. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;The above unconditional purchase obligations also include other product supply commitments and also electric power and natural gas supply purchase obligations. In addition, purchase commitments to spend approximately $&lt;font class="_mt"&gt;330&lt;/font&gt; for additional plant and equipment are included in the unconditional purchase obligations in 2011. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;</NonNumbericText>
          <NonNumericTextHeader>17.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Commitments and Contingencies


Litigation
The Company is involved in various legal proceedings, including competition, environmental, health,</NonNumericTextHeader>
          <FootnoteIndexer />
          <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
          <hasScenarios>false</hasScenarios>
          <DisplayDateInUSFormat>false</DisplayDateInUSFormat>
        </Cell>
      </Cells>
      <OriginalInstanceReportColumns />
      <ElementDataType>us-types:textBlockItemType</ElementDataType>
      <SimpleDataType>textblock</SimpleDataType>
      <ElementDefenition>Includes disclosure of commitments and contingencies. This element may be used as a single block of text to encapsulate the entire disclosure including data and tables.</ElementDefenition>
      <ElementReferences>Reference 1: http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/presentationRef
 -Publisher FASB
 -Name FASB Interpretation (FIN)
 -Number 14
 -Paragraph 3

Reference 2: http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/presentationRef
 -Publisher FASB
 -Name Statement of Financial Accounting Standard (FAS)
 -Number 5
 -Paragraph 9, 10, 11, 12

</ElementReferences>
      <IsTotalLabel>false</IsTotalLabel>
    </Row>
  </Rows>
  <Footnotes />
  <NumberOfCols>1</NumberOfCols>
  <NumberOfRows>2</NumberOfRows>
  <HasScenarios>false</HasScenarios>
  <MonetaryRoundingLevel>UnKnown</MonetaryRoundingLevel>
  <SharesRoundingLevel>UnKnown</SharesRoundingLevel>
  <PerShareRoundingLevel>UnKnown</PerShareRoundingLevel>
  <HasPureData>false</HasPureData>
  <SharesShouldBeRounded>true</SharesShouldBeRounded>
</InstanceReport>
</XBRL>
</TEXT>

</DOCUMENT>