
<DOCUMENT>
<TYPE>XML
<SEQUENCE>131
<FILENAME>R9.xml
<DESCRIPTION>IDEA: New Accounting Guidance
<TEXT>
<XBRL>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<InstanceReport xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Version>2.2.0.7</Version>
  <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
  <ReportName>New Accounting Guidance</ReportName>
  <ReportLongName>10201 - Disclosure - New Accounting Guidance</ReportLongName>
  <DisplayLabelColumn>true</DisplayLabelColumn>
  <ShowElementNames>false</ShowElementNames>
  <RoundingOption />
  <HasEmbeddedReports>false</HasEmbeddedReports>
  <Columns>
    <Column>
      <LabelColumn>false</LabelColumn>
      <Id>1</Id>
      <Labels>
        <Label Id="1" Label="12 Months Ended" />
        <Label Id="2" Label="Sep. 30, 2010" />
      </Labels>
      <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
      <FootnoteIndexer />
      <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
      <hasScenarios>false</hasScenarios>
      <Segments />
      <Scenarios />
      <Units>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>Unit1</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Standard</UnitType>
          <StandardMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/iso4217</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>USD</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>iso4217</MeasureNamespace>
          </StandardMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>Unit13</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Standard</UnitType>
          <StandardMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>pure</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>xbrli</MeasureNamespace>
          </StandardMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>Unit15</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Standard</UnitType>
          <StandardMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>shares</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>xbrli</MeasureNamespace>
          </StandardMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>Unit12</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Divide</UnitType>
          <NumeratorMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/iso4217</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>USD</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>iso4217</MeasureNamespace>
          </NumeratorMeasure>
          <DenominatorMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>shares</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>xbrli</MeasureNamespace>
          </DenominatorMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
      </Units>
      <CurrencySymbol>$</CurrencySymbol>
    </Column>
  </Columns>
  <Rows>
    <Row>
      <Id>2</Id>
      <Label>New Accounting Guidance</Label>
      <Level>0</Level>
      <ElementName>us-gaap_NewAccountingPronouncementsAndChangesInAccountingPrinciplesAbstract</ElementName>
      <ElementPrefix>us-gaap</ElementPrefix>
      <IsBaseElement>true</IsBaseElement>
      <BalanceType>na</BalanceType>
      <PeriodType>duration</PeriodType>
      <ShortDefinition>No definition available.</ShortDefinition>
      <IsReportTitle>false</IsReportTitle>
      <IsSegmentTitle>false</IsSegmentTitle>
      <IsSubReportEnd>false</IsSubReportEnd>
      <IsCalendarTitle>false</IsCalendarTitle>
      <IsTuple>false</IsTuple>
      <IsAbstractGroupTitle>true</IsAbstractGroupTitle>
      <IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>false</IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>
      <IsEquityAdjustmentRow>false</IsEquityAdjustmentRow>
      <IsBeginningBalance>false</IsBeginningBalance>
      <IsEndingBalance>false</IsEndingBalance>
      <IsReverseSign>false</IsReverseSign>
      <PreferredLabelRole />
      <IsEPS>false</IsEPS>
      <FootnoteIndexer />
      <Cells>
        <Cell>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <ShowCurrencySymbol>false</ShowCurrencySymbol>
          <IsNumeric>false</IsNumeric>
          <IsRatio>false</IsRatio>
          <DisplayZeroAsNone>false</DisplayZeroAsNone>
          <NumericAmount>0</NumericAmount>
          <RoundedNumericAmount>0</RoundedNumericAmount>
          <NonNumbericText />
          <NonNumericTextHeader />
          <FootnoteIndexer />
          <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
          <hasScenarios>false</hasScenarios>
          <DisplayDateInUSFormat>false</DisplayDateInUSFormat>
        </Cell>
      </Cells>
      <OriginalInstanceReportColumns />
      <ElementDataType>xbrli:stringItemType</ElementDataType>
      <SimpleDataType>string</SimpleDataType>
      <ElementDefenition>No definition available.</ElementDefenition>
      <IsTotalLabel>false</IsTotalLabel>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <Id>3</Id>
      <Label>New Accounting Guidance</Label>
      <Level>1</Level>
      <ElementName>us-gaap_ScheduleOfNewAccountingPronouncementsAndChangesInAccountingPrinciplesTextBlock</ElementName>
      <ElementPrefix>us-gaap</ElementPrefix>
      <IsBaseElement>true</IsBaseElement>
      <BalanceType>na</BalanceType>
      <PeriodType>duration</PeriodType>
      <ShortDefinition>No definition available.</ShortDefinition>
      <IsReportTitle>false</IsReportTitle>
      <IsSegmentTitle>false</IsSegmentTitle>
      <IsSubReportEnd>false</IsSubReportEnd>
      <IsCalendarTitle>false</IsCalendarTitle>
      <IsTuple>false</IsTuple>
      <IsAbstractGroupTitle>false</IsAbstractGroupTitle>
      <IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>false</IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>
      <IsEquityAdjustmentRow>false</IsEquityAdjustmentRow>
      <IsBeginningBalance>false</IsBeginningBalance>
      <IsEndingBalance>false</IsEndingBalance>
      <IsReverseSign>false</IsReverseSign>
      <PreferredLabelRole>verboselabel</PreferredLabelRole>
      <IsEPS>false</IsEPS>
      <FootnoteIndexer />
      <Cells>
        <Cell>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <ShowCurrencySymbol>false</ShowCurrencySymbol>
          <IsNumeric>false</IsNumeric>
          <IsRatio>false</IsRatio>
          <DisplayZeroAsNone>false</DisplayZeroAsNone>
          <NumericAmount>0</NumericAmount>
          <RoundedNumericAmount>0</RoundedNumericAmount>
          <NonNumbericText>&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p style="margin-top: 18px; margin-bottom: 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: Times New Roman;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a name="fin17525_2"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 12px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a name="tx17525_23"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;New Accounting Guidance &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Accounting Guidance to be Implemented &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;C&lt;small&gt;ONSOLIDATION&lt;/small&gt; &lt;small&gt;OF&lt;/small&gt; V&lt;small&gt;ARIABLE&lt;/small&gt; I&lt;small&gt;NTEREST&lt;/small&gt; E&lt;small&gt;NTITIES&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In June 2009, the Financial Accounting Standards Board (FASB) issued authoritative guidance that amends previous guidance for determining whether an entity is a variable interest entity (VIE). It requires an enterprise to perform an analysis to determine whether the Company's variable interests give it a controlling financial interest in a VIE. A company would be required to assess whether it has an implicit financial responsibility to ensure that a VIE operates as designed when determining whether it has the power to direct the activities of the VIE that most significantly impact the entity's economic performance. In addition, ongoing reassessments of whether an enterprise is the primary beneficiary of a VIE are required. This guidance is effective for the Company for fiscal year 2011. The adoption of this guidance will not have a material impact on the Company's consolidated financial statements. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;
/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin-top: 6px; margin-bottom: 0px; font-size: 1px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;M&lt;small&gt;ULTIPLE&lt;/small&gt;-D&lt;small&gt;ELIVERABLE&lt;/small&gt; R&lt;small&gt;EVENUE&lt;/small&gt; A&lt;small&gt;RRANGEMENTS&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In October 2009, the FASB issued authoritative guidance on multiple-deliverable revenue arrangements. This new guidance amends the existing criteria for separating consideration received in multiple-deliverable arrangements and requires that arrangement consideration be allocated at the inception of the arrangement to all deliverables based on their relative selling price. The guidance establishes a hierarchy for determining the selling price of a deliverable which is based on vendor-specific objective evidence, third-party evidence, or management estimates. Expanded disclosures related to multiple-deliverable revenue arrangements are also required. This guidance is effective for the Company for fiscal year 2011. Upon adoption, the guidance may be applied either prospectively from the beginning of the fiscal year for new or materially modified arrangements, or it may be applied retrospectively. The adoption of this 
guidance will not have a material impact on the Company's consolidated financial statements. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accounting Guidance Implemented &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;B&lt;small&gt;USINESS&lt;/small&gt; C&lt;small&gt;OMBINATIONS&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In December&amp;nbsp;2007, the FASB issued authoritative guidance to affirm that the acquisition method of accounting (previously referred to as the purchase method) be used for all business combinations and for an acquirer to be identified for each business combination. This guidance defines the acquirer as the entity that obtains control of one or more businesses in the business combination and establishes the acquisition date as the date that the acquirer achieves control. Among other requirements, the guidance requires the acquiring entity in a business combination to recognize at full fair value all the assets acquired and liabilities assumed in the transaction. If a business combination is achieved in stages, the previously-held ownership interest is adjusted to fair value at the acquisition date, and any resulting gain or loss is recognized in earnings. Contingent consideration is recognized at fair value at 
the acquisition date, and restructuring and acquisition-related costs are expensed as incurred. The fair value of assets and liabilities acquired, including uncertain tax positions, can be adjusted during the measurement period. Any adjustments after the measurement period, which cannot exceed one year, will be recognized in earnings. This guidance was effective for the Company beginning on 1&amp;nbsp;October&amp;nbsp;2009 and was applied prospectively. The adoption of this guidance did not have a material impact on the Company's 2010&amp;nbsp;consolidated financial statements. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;N&lt;small&gt;ONCONTROLLING&lt;/small&gt; I&lt;small&gt;NTERESTS&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In December 2007, the FASB issued authoritative guidance that establishes the accounting and reporting standards for the noncontrolling interests in a subsidiary and for the deconsolidation of a subsidiary. It requires entities to report noncontrolling interests in subsidiaries separately within equity in the consolidated balance sheets. It also requires disclosure, on the face of the consolidated income statement, of the amounts of consolidated net income attributable to the parent and noncontrolling interests. Changes in a parent's ownership interests while the parent retains control are treated as equity transactions. If a parent loses control of a subsidiary, any retained noncontrolling interests would be measured at fair value, with any gain or loss recognized in earnings. This guidance was effective for the Company on 1&amp;nbsp;October 2009 and was applied prospectively, except for the presentation and disclo
sure requirements related to noncontrolling interests, which were applied retrospectively for all periods presented. The Company's consolidated financial statements have been updated to reflect the new presentation. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;F&lt;small&gt;AIR&lt;/small&gt; V&lt;small&gt;ALUE&lt;/small&gt; M&lt;small&gt;EASUREMENTS&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In September&amp;nbsp;2006, the FASB issued authoritative guidance that defines fair value, establishes a framework for measuring fair value, and expands disclosures about fair value measurements. Effective 1 October&amp;nbsp;2008, the Company adopted this guidance for financial assets and liabilities and any other assets and liabilities that are recognized and disclosed at fair value on a recurring basis. The requirement for other nonfinancial assets and liabilities was effective on 1&amp;nbsp;October&amp;nbsp;2009 for the Company. This guidance did not impact the Company's consolidated financial statements upon adoption. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 6px 1% 0px;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In January 2010, the FASB issued authoritative guidance on improving disclosures about fair value measurements. This guidance requires new disclosures about transfers in and out of Level 1 and 2 measurements and separate disclosures about activity relating to Level 3 measurements. In addition, this guidance clarifies existing fair value disclosures about the level of disaggregation and the input and valuation techniques used to measure fair value. The guidance only relates to disclosure and does not impact the Company's consolidated financial statements. The Company adopted this guidance in the second quarter of fiscal year 2010. There was no significant impact to the Company's disclosures upon adoption. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin-top: 6px; margin-bottom: 0px; font-size: 1px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;E&lt;small&gt;MPLOYERS&lt;/small&gt;' D&lt;small&gt;ISCLOSURES&lt;/small&gt; &lt;small&gt;ABOUT&lt;/small&gt; P&lt;small&gt;OSTRETIREMENT&lt;/small&gt; B&lt;small&gt;ENEFIT&lt;/small&gt; P&lt;small&gt;LAN&lt;/small&gt; A&lt;small&gt;SSETS&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 1%;"&gt;&lt;font style="font-family: ARIAL;" class="_mt" size="2"&gt;In December 2008, the FASB issued authoritative guidance to require employers to provide additional disclosures about plan assets of a defined benefit or other postretirement plan. Disclosures include information about investment policies and strategies, major categories of plan assets, the inputs and valuation techniques used to measure the fair value of plan assets, and significant concentrations of risk. This guidance was effective for the Company beginning with its fiscal year-end 2010. Upon adoption, this guidance was not required to be applied to earlier periods that are presented for comparative purposes. This guidance only requires additional disclosure and did not have an impact on the Company's consolidated financial statements upon adoption. Refer to Note 16, Retirement Benefits, for the required disclosures. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;</NonNumbericText>
          <NonNumericTextHeader>2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;New Accounting Guidance
New Accounting Guidance to be Implemented
CONSOLIDATION OF VARIABLE INTEREST ENTITIES
In June 2009, the Financial</NonNumericTextHeader>
          <FootnoteIndexer />
          <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
          <hasScenarios>false</hasScenarios>
          <DisplayDateInUSFormat>false</DisplayDateInUSFormat>
        </Cell>
      </Cells>
      <OriginalInstanceReportColumns />
      <ElementDataType>us-types:textBlockItemType</ElementDataType>
      <SimpleDataType>textblock</SimpleDataType>
      <ElementDefenition>Represents disclosure of any changes in an accounting principle, including a change from one generally accepted accounting principle to another generally accepted accounting principle when there are two or more generally accepted accounting principles that apply or when the accounting principle formerly used is no longer generally accepted. Also disclose any change in the method of applying an accounting principle, or any change in an accounting principle required by a new pronouncement in the unusual instance that a new pronouncement does not include specific transition provisions.</ElementDefenition>
      <ElementReferences>Reference 1: http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/presentationRef
 -Publisher FASB
 -Name Statement of Financial Accounting Standard (FAS)
 -Number 154
 -Paragraph 2, 17, 18

Reference 2: http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/presentationRef
 -Publisher AICPA
 -Name Accounting Principles Board Opinion (APB)
 -Number 28
 -Paragraph 23, 24

Reference 3: http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/presentationRef
 -Publisher SEC
 -Name Regulation S-X (SX)
 -Number 210
 -Section 01
 -Paragraph b
 -Subparagraph 6
 -Article 10

</ElementReferences>
      <IsTotalLabel>false</IsTotalLabel>
    </Row>
  </Rows>
  <Footnotes />
  <NumberOfCols>1</NumberOfCols>
  <NumberOfRows>2</NumberOfRows>
  <HasScenarios>false</HasScenarios>
  <MonetaryRoundingLevel>UnKnown</MonetaryRoundingLevel>
  <SharesRoundingLevel>UnKnown</SharesRoundingLevel>
  <PerShareRoundingLevel>UnKnown</PerShareRoundingLevel>
  <HasPureData>false</HasPureData>
  <SharesShouldBeRounded>true</SharesShouldBeRounded>
</InstanceReport>
</XBRL>
</TEXT>

</DOCUMENT>