
<DOCUMENT>
<TYPE>XML
<SEQUENCE>19
<FILENAME>R8.xml
<DESCRIPTION>IDEA: Summary of Significant Accounting Policies
<TEXT>
<XBRL>
﻿<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<InstanceReport xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Version>2.2.0.7</Version>
  <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
  <ReportName>Summary of Significant Accounting Policies</ReportName>
  <ReportLongName>0202 - Disclosure - Summary of Significant Accounting Policies</ReportLongName>
  <DisplayLabelColumn>true</DisplayLabelColumn>
  <ShowElementNames>false</ShowElementNames>
  <RoundingOption />
  <HasEmbeddedReports>false</HasEmbeddedReports>
  <Columns>
    <Column>
      <LabelColumn>false</LabelColumn>
      <Id>1</Id>
      <Labels>
        <Label Id="1" Label="12 Months Ended" />
        <Label Id="2" Label="Oct. 01, 2010" />
      </Labels>
      <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
      <FootnoteIndexer />
      <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
      <hasScenarios>false</hasScenarios>
      <Segments />
      <Scenarios />
      <Units>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>USD</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Standard</UnitType>
          <StandardMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/iso4217</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>USD</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>iso4217</MeasureNamespace>
          </StandardMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>USDEPS</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Divide</UnitType>
          <NumeratorMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/iso4217</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>USD</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>iso4217</MeasureNamespace>
          </NumeratorMeasure>
          <DenominatorMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>shares</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>xbrli</MeasureNamespace>
          </DenominatorMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
        <Unit>
          <UnitID>Shares</UnitID>
          <UnitType>Standard</UnitType>
          <StandardMeasure>
            <MeasureSchema>http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance</MeasureSchema>
            <MeasureValue>shares</MeasureValue>
            <MeasureNamespace>xbrli</MeasureNamespace>
          </StandardMeasure>
          <Scale>0</Scale>
        </Unit>
      </Units>
      <CurrencySymbol>$</CurrencySymbol>
    </Column>
  </Columns>
  <Rows>
    <Row>
      <Id>2</Id>
      <Label>Summary of Significant Accounting Policies [Abstract]</Label>
      <Level>0</Level>
      <ElementName>swks_SummaryOfSignificantAccountingPoliciesAbstract</ElementName>
      <ElementPrefix>swks</ElementPrefix>
      <IsBaseElement>false</IsBaseElement>
      <BalanceType>na</BalanceType>
      <PeriodType>duration</PeriodType>
      <ShortDefinition>Summary of Significant Accounting Policies.</ShortDefinition>
      <IsReportTitle>false</IsReportTitle>
      <IsSegmentTitle>false</IsSegmentTitle>
      <IsSubReportEnd>false</IsSubReportEnd>
      <IsCalendarTitle>false</IsCalendarTitle>
      <IsTuple>false</IsTuple>
      <IsAbstractGroupTitle>true</IsAbstractGroupTitle>
      <IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>false</IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>
      <IsEquityAdjustmentRow>false</IsEquityAdjustmentRow>
      <IsBeginningBalance>false</IsBeginningBalance>
      <IsEndingBalance>false</IsEndingBalance>
      <IsReverseSign>false</IsReverseSign>
      <PreferredLabelRole />
      <IsEPS>false</IsEPS>
      <FootnoteIndexer />
      <Cells>
        <Cell>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <ShowCurrencySymbol>false</ShowCurrencySymbol>
          <IsNumeric>false</IsNumeric>
          <IsRatio>false</IsRatio>
          <DisplayZeroAsNone>false</DisplayZeroAsNone>
          <NumericAmount>0</NumericAmount>
          <RoundedNumericAmount>0</RoundedNumericAmount>
          <NonNumbericText />
          <NonNumericTextHeader />
          <FootnoteIndexer />
          <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
          <hasScenarios>false</hasScenarios>
          <DisplayDateInUSFormat>false</DisplayDateInUSFormat>
        </Cell>
      </Cells>
      <OriginalInstanceReportColumns />
      <ElementDataType>xbrli:stringItemType</ElementDataType>
      <SimpleDataType>string</SimpleDataType>
      <ElementDefenition>Summary of Significant Accounting Policies.</ElementDefenition>
      <IsTotalLabel>false</IsTotalLabel>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <Id>3</Id>
      <Label>SUMMARY OF SIGNIFICANT ACCOUNTING POLICIES</Label>
      <Level>1</Level>
      <ElementName>us-gaap_SignificantAccountingPoliciesTextBlock</ElementName>
      <ElementPrefix>us-gaap</ElementPrefix>
      <IsBaseElement>true</IsBaseElement>
      <BalanceType>na</BalanceType>
      <PeriodType>duration</PeriodType>
      <ShortDefinition>No definition available.</ShortDefinition>
      <IsReportTitle>false</IsReportTitle>
      <IsSegmentTitle>false</IsSegmentTitle>
      <IsSubReportEnd>false</IsSubReportEnd>
      <IsCalendarTitle>false</IsCalendarTitle>
      <IsTuple>false</IsTuple>
      <IsAbstractGroupTitle>false</IsAbstractGroupTitle>
      <IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>false</IsEquityPrevioslyReportedAsRow>
      <IsEquityAdjustmentRow>false</IsEquityAdjustmentRow>
      <IsBeginningBalance>false</IsBeginningBalance>
      <IsEndingBalance>false</IsEndingBalance>
      <IsReverseSign>false</IsReverseSign>
      <PreferredLabelRole>verboselabel</PreferredLabelRole>
      <IsEPS>false</IsEPS>
      <FootnoteIndexer />
      <Cells>
        <Cell>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <ShowCurrencySymbol>false</ShowCurrencySymbol>
          <IsNumeric>false</IsNumeric>
          <IsRatio>false</IsRatio>
          <DisplayZeroAsNone>false</DisplayZeroAsNone>
          <NumericAmount>0</NumericAmount>
          <RoundedNumericAmount>0</RoundedNumericAmount>
          <NonNumbericText>&lt;!--DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd" --&gt;
   &lt;!-- Begin Block Tagged Note 2 - us-gaap:SignificantAccountingPoliciesTextBlock--&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-family: 'Times New Roman',Times,serif"&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;2. SUMMARY OF SIGNIFICANT ACCOUNTING POLICIES&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;PRINCIPLES OF CONSOLIDATION&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;All majority owned subsidiaries are included in the Company&amp;#8217;s Consolidated Financial Statements and
   all intercompany balances are eliminated in consolidation.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;FISCAL YEAR&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The Company&amp;#8217;s fiscal year ends on the Friday closest to September&amp;#160;30. Fiscal years 2010 and 2009
   each consisted of 52&amp;#160;weeks and ended on October&amp;#160;1, 2010 and October&amp;#160;2, 2009, respectively. Fiscal
   year 2008 consisted of 53&amp;#160;weeks and ended on October&amp;#160;3, 2008.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;USE OF ESTIMATES&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The preparation of consolidated financial statements in conformity with accounting principles
   generally accepted in the United States requires management to make estimates and assumptions that
   affect the reported amounts of assets and liabilities and disclosure of contingent liabilities at
   the date of the financial statements and the reported amounts of revenues and expenses during the
   reporting period. On an ongoing basis, management reviews its estimates based upon currently
   available information. Actual results could differ materially from those estimates.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;REVENUE RECOGNITION&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Revenues from product sales are recognized upon shipment and transfer of title, in accordance with
   the shipping terms specified in the arrangement with the customer. Revenue from license fees and
   intellectual property is recognized when due and payable, and all other criteria of ASC 605-&lt;i&gt;Revenue
   Recognition, &lt;/i&gt;have been met. The Company ships product on consignment to certain customers and only
   recognize revenue when the customer notifies us that the inventory has been consumed. Revenue
   recognition is deferred in all instances where the earnings process is incomplete. Certain product
   sales are made to electronic component distributors under agreements allowing for price protection
   and/or a right of return (stock rotation) on unsold products. A reserve for sales returns and
   allowances for customers is recorded based on historical experience or specific identification of a
   contractual arrangement necessitating a revenue reserve.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ALLOWANCE FOR DOUBTFUL ACCOUNTS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The Company maintains general allowances for doubtful accounts for losses that they estimate will
   arise from their customers&amp;#8217; inability to make required payments. These reserves require management
   to apply judgment in deriving estimates. As the Company becomes aware of any specific receivables
   which may be uncollectable, they perform additional analysis and reserves are recorded if deemed
   necessary. Determination of such additional specific reserves require management to make judgments
   and estimates pertaining to factors such as a customer&amp;#8217;s credit worthiness, intent and ability to
   pay, and overall financial position. If the data the Company uses to calculate the
   allowance for doubtful accounts does not reflect the future ability to collect outstanding
   receivables, additional provisions for doubtful accounts may be needed and its results of
   operations could be materially affected.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;CASH AND CASH EQUIVALENTS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The Company&amp;#8217;s cash and cash equivalents primarily consist of cash money market funds and repurchase
   agreements where the underlying securities primarily consist of United States treasury obligations,
   United States agency obligations, overnight repurchase agreements backed by United States
   treasuries and/or United States agency obligations and highly rated commercial paper.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;INVESTMENTS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The Company&amp;#8217;s investment is classified as available for sale and consists of an auction rate
   security (&amp;#8220;ARS&amp;#8221;).
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;RESTRICTED CASH&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Restricted cash is primarily used to collateralize the Company&amp;#8217;s obligation under
   the Credit Facility, which management plans to repay during the first
   quarter of fiscal 2011.
    For further information regarding the Credit Facility, please see Note 9 to the Consolidated Financial Statements.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;INVENTORIES&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Inventories are stated at the lower of cost, determined on a first-in, first-out basis, or market.
   Each quarter, the Company estimates and establishes reserves for excess, obsolete or unmarketable
   inventory. These reserves are generally equal to the historical cost basis of the excess or
   obsolete inventory and once recorded are considered permanent adjustments. Calculation of the
   reserves requires management to use judgment and make assumptions about forecasted demand in
   relation to the inventory on hand, competitiveness of its product offerings, general market
   conditions and product life cycles upon which the reserves are based. When inventory on hand
   exceeds foreseeable demand (generally in excess of twelve months), reserves are established for the
   value of such inventory that is not expected to be sold at the time of the review.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;If actual demand and market conditions are less favorable than those the Company projects,
   additional inventory reserves may be required and its results of operations could be materially
   affected. Some or all of the inventories that have been reserved may be retained and made available
   for sale; however, they are generally scrapped over time.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;PROPERTY, PLANT AND EQUIPMENT&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Property, plant and equipment are carried at cost less accumulated depreciation and amortization.
   Depreciation is calculated using the straight-line method. Significant renewals and betterments are
   capitalized and equipment taken out of service is written off. Maintenance and repairs, as well as
   renewals of a minor amount, are expensed as incurred.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Estimated useful lives used for depreciation purposes are 5 to 30&amp;#160;years for buildings and
   improvements and 3 to 10&amp;#160;years for machinery and equipment. Leasehold improvements are depreciated
   over the lesser of the economic life or the life of the associated lease.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SHARE-BASED COMPENSATION&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The Company applies ASC 718 &lt;i&gt;Compensation-Stock Compensation &lt;/i&gt;(&amp;#8220;ASC 718&amp;#8221;) which requires the
   measurement and recognition of compensation expense for all share-based payment awards made to
   employees and directors including employee stock options, employee stock purchases related to the
   Company&amp;#8217;s 2002 Employee Stock Purchase Plan, restricted stock
   and other special share-based awards based
   on estimated fair values. The Company
   adopted ASC 718 using the modified prospective transition method, which requires the application of
   the applicable accounting standard as of October&amp;#160;1, 2005, the first day of the Company&amp;#8217;s fiscal
   year 2006.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The fair value of stock-based awards is amortized over the requisite service period, which is
   defined as the period during which an employee is required to provide service in exchange for an
   award. The Company uses a straight-line attribution method for all grants that
   include only a service condition. Due to the existence of both performance and service
   conditions, certain restricted stock grants are expensed over the service period for each
   separately vesting tranche.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Share-based compensation expense recognized during the period is based on the value of the portion
   of share-based payment awards that is ultimately expected to vest during the period. Share-based
   compensation expense recognized in the Company&amp;#8217;s Consolidated Statement of Operations for the
   fiscal year ended October&amp;#160;1, 2010 only included share-based payment awards granted subsequent to
   September&amp;#160;30, 2005 based on the grant date fair value estimated in accordance with the provisions
   of ASC 718. As share-based compensation expense recognized in the Consolidated Statement of
   Operations for the fiscal year ended October&amp;#160;1, 2010 is based on awards ultimately expected to
   vest, it has been reduced for estimated forfeitures. ASC 718 requires forfeitures to be estimated
   at the time of grant and revised, if necessary, in subsequent periods if actual forfeitures differ
   from those estimates.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Upon adoption of ASC 718, the Company elected to retain its method of valuation for share-based
   awards using the Black-Scholes option-pricing model (&amp;#8220;Black-Scholes model&amp;#8221;) which was also
   previously used for the Company&amp;#8217;s pro forma information required under the previous authoritative
   literature governing stock compensation expense. The Company&amp;#8217;s determination of fair value of
   share-based payment awards on the date of grant using the Black-Scholes model is affected by the
   Company&amp;#8217;s stock price as well as assumptions regarding a number of highly complex and subjective
   variables. These variables include, but are not limited to; the Company&amp;#8217;s expected stock price
   volatility over the term of the awards, and actual and projected employee stock option exercise
   behaviors. For more complex awards with market-based performance conditions, the Company employs a
   Monte Carlo simulation method which calculates many potential outcomes for an award and establishes
   fair value based on the most likely outcome.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;VALUATION OF LONG-LIVED ASSETS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Carrying values for long-lived assets and definite lived intangible assets, which exclude goodwill,
   are reviewed for possible impairment as circumstances warrant. Factors considered important that
   could result in an impairment review include significant underperformance relative to expected,
   historical or projected future operating results, significant changes in the manner of use of
   assets or the Company&amp;#8217;s business strategy, significant negative industry or economic trends and a
   significant decline in its stock price for a sustained period of time. In addition, impairment
   reviews are conducted at the judgment of management whenever asset / asset group values are deemed
   to be unrecoverable relative to future undiscounted cash flows expected to be generated by that
   particular asset / asset group. The determination of recoverability is based on an estimate of
   undiscounted cash flows expected to result from the use of an asset / asset group and its eventual
   disposition. Such estimates require management to exercise judgment and make assumptions regarding
   factors such as future revenue streams, operating expenditures, cost allocation and asset
   utilization levels, all of which collectively impact future operating performance. The Company&amp;#8217;s
   estimates of undiscounted cash flows may differ from actual cash flows due to, among other things,
   technological changes, economic conditions, changes to its business model or changes in its
   operating performance. If the sum of the undiscounted cash flows (excluding interest) is less than
   the carrying value of an asset/asset group, the Company would recognize an impairment loss,
   measured as the amount by which the carrying value exceeds the fair value of the asset or asset
   group.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;GOODWILL AND INTANGIBLE ASSETS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Goodwill and intangible assets with indefinite useful lives are tested at least annually for
   impairment in accordance with the provisions of ASC 350 &lt;i&gt;Intangibles-Goodwill and Other &lt;/i&gt;(&amp;#8220;ASC 350&amp;#8221;)&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;
   Intangible assets with indefinite useful lives comprise an insignificant portion of the total book
   value of the Company&amp;#8217;s goodwill and intangible assets. The Company assesses the need to test its
   goodwill for impairment on a regular basis. Pursuant to the guidance provided under ASC 280-&lt;i&gt;Segment
   Reporting &lt;/i&gt;(&amp;#8220;ASC 280&amp;#8221;), the Company has determined that it has only one reporting unit for the
   purposes of allocating and testing goodwill under ASC 350.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;!-- Folio --&gt;
   &lt;!-- /Folio --&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;!-- PAGEBREAK --&gt;
   &lt;div style="font-family: 'Times New Roman',Times,serif"&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The goodwill impairment test is a two-step process. The first step of the Company&amp;#8217;s impairment
   analysis compares its fair value to its net book value to determine if there is an indicator of
   impairment. To determine fair value, ASC 350 allows for the use of several valuation methodologies,
   although it states that quoted market prices are the best evidence of fair value and shall be used
   as the basis for measuring fair value where available. In the Company&amp;#8217;s assessment of its fair
   value, the Company considers the average market price of its common stock surrounding the selected
   testing date, the number of shares of its common stock outstanding during such period and other
   marketplace activity and related control premiums. If the calculated fair value is determined to be
   less than the book value of the Company, then the Company performs step two of the impairment
   analysis. Step two of the analysis compares the implied fair value of the Company&amp;#8217;s goodwill, to
   the book value of its goodwill. If the book value of the Company&amp;#8217;s goodwill exceeds the implied
   fair value of its goodwill, an impairment loss is recognized equal to that excess. In step two of
   the Company&amp;#8217;s annual impairment analysis, the Company primarily uses the income approach
   methodology of valuation, which includes the discounted cash flow method as well as other generally
   accepted valuation methodologies, to determine the implied fair value of the Company&amp;#8217;s goodwill.
   Significant management judgment is required in preparing the forecasts of future operating results
   that are used in the discounted cash flow method of valuation. Should step two of the impairment
   test be required, the estimates management would use would be consistent with the plans and
   estimates that the Company uses to manage its business. In addition to testing goodwill for
   impairment on an annual basis, factors such as unexpected adverse business conditions,
   deterioration of the economic climate, unanticipated technological changes, adverse changes in the
   competitive environment, loss of key personnel and acts by governments and courts, are considered
   by management and may signal that the Company&amp;#8217;s intangible assets have become impaired and result
   in additional interim impairment testing.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;In fiscal year 2010, the Company performed impairment tests of its goodwill as of the first day of
   the fourth fiscal quarter in accordance with the Company&amp;#8217;s regularly scheduled annual testing. The
   results of this test indicated that none of the Company&amp;#8217;s goodwill was impaired based on step one
   of the test; accordingly step two of the test was not performed.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;DEFERRED FINANCING COSTS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Financing costs are capitalized as an asset on the Company&amp;#8217;s balance sheet and amortized on a
   straight-line basis over the life of the financing. If debt is extinguished early, a proportionate
   amount of deferred financing costs is charged to earnings.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;INCOME TAXES&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The Company uses the asset and liability method of accounting for income taxes. Under the asset and
   liability method, deferred tax assets and liabilities are recognized for the estimated future tax
   consequences attributable to differences between the financial statement carrying amounts of
   existing assets and liabilities and their respective tax basis. This method also requires the
   recognition of future tax benefits such as net operating loss carry forwards, to the extent that
   realization of such benefits is more likely than not. Deferred tax assets and liabilities are
   measured using enacted tax rates expected to apply to taxable income in the years in which those
   temporary differences are expected to be recovered or settled. The effect on deferred tax assets
   and liabilities of a change in tax rates is recognized in income in the period that includes the
   enactment date.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The carrying value of the Company&amp;#8217;s net deferred tax assets assumes the Company will be able to
   generate sufficient future taxable income in certain tax jurisdictions, based on estimates and
   assumptions. If these estimates and related assumptions change in the future, the Company may be
   required to record additional valuation allowances against its deferred tax assets resulting in
   additional income tax expense in its consolidated statement of operations. Management evaluates the
   realizability of the deferred tax assets and assesses the adequacy of the valuation allowance
   quarterly. Likewise, in the event the Company were to determine that it would be able to realize
   its deferred tax assets in the future in excess of their net recorded amount, an adjustment to the
   deferred tax assets would increase income or decrease the carrying value of goodwill in the period
   such determination was made.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The determination of recording or releasing tax valuation allowances is made, in part, pursuant to
   an assessment performed by management regarding the likelihood that the Company will generate
   future taxable income against
   which benefits of its deferred tax assets may or may not be realized. This assessment requires
   management to exercise significant judgment and make estimates with respect to its ability to
   generate revenues, gross profits, operating income and taxable income in future periods. Amongst
   other factors, management must make assumptions regarding overall business and semiconductor
   industry conditions, operating efficiencies, the Company&amp;#8217;s ability to develop products to its
   customers&amp;#8217; specifications, technological change, the competitive environment and changes in
   regulatory requirements which may impact its ability to generate taxable income and, in turn,
   realize the value of its deferred tax assets. In addition, the current uncertain economic
   environment limits the Company&amp;#8217;s ability to confidently forecast its taxable income. In fiscal
   years 2010 and 2009, the Company&amp;#8217;s estimates of future taxable income were prepared in a manner
   consistent with its assessment of various factors, including market and industry conditions,
   operating trends, product life cycles and competitive and regulatory environments.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The calculation of the Company&amp;#8217;s tax liabilities includes addressing uncertainties in the
   application of complex tax regulations. With the implementation effective September&amp;#160;29, 2007, ASC
   740 (formerly referenced as FASB Interpretation No.&amp;#160;48, &lt;i&gt;Accounting for Uncertainty in Income
   Taxes-an interpretation of FASB Statement No.&amp;#160;109&lt;/i&gt;), clarifies the accounting for uncertainty in
   income taxes recognized in an enterprise&amp;#8217;s financial statements in accordance with GAAP. ASC 740
   prescribes a recognition threshold and measurement attribute for the financial statement
   recognition and measurement of a tax position taken or expected to be taken in a tax return.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The Company recognizes liabilities for anticipated tax audit issues in the United States and other
   tax jurisdictions based on its recognition threshold and measurement attribute of whether it is
   more likely than not that the positions the Company has taken in tax filings will be sustained upon
   tax audit, and the extent to which, additional taxes would be due. If payment of these amounts
   ultimately proves to be unnecessary, the reversal of the liabilities would result in tax benefits
   being recognized in the period in which it is determined the liabilities are no longer necessary.
   If the estimate of tax liabilities proves to be less than the ultimate assessment, a further charge
   to expense would result.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT COSTS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;Research and development costs are expensed as incurred.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;FINANCIAL INSTRUMENTS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The carrying value of cash and cash equivalents, accounts receivable, other current assets,
   accounts payable, short-term debt and accrued liabilities approximates fair value due to short-term
   maturities of these assets and liabilities. Fair values of long-term debt and investments are based
   on quoted market prices if available, and if not available a fair value is determined through a
   discounted cash flow analysis at the date of measurement.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ACCUMULATED OTHER COMPREHENSIVE LOSS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;The Company accounts for comprehensive loss in accordance with the provisions of ASC 220 -
   &lt;i&gt;Comprehensive Income &lt;/i&gt;(&amp;#8220;ASC 220&amp;#8221;). ASC 220 is a financial statement presentation standard that
   requires the Company to disclose non-owner changes included in equity but not included in net
   income or loss. Accumulated other comprehensive loss presented in the financial statements consists
   of adjustments to the Company&amp;#8217;s auction rate securities and minimum pension liability as follows
   (in thousands):
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;!-- Folio --&gt;
   &lt;!-- /Folio --&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;!-- PAGEBREAK --&gt;
   &lt;div style="font-family: 'Times New Roman',Times,serif"&gt;
   &lt;div align="center"&gt;
   &lt;table style="font-size: 10pt; text-align: left" cellspacing="0" border="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%"&gt;
   &lt;!-- Begin Table Head --&gt;
   &lt;tr valign="bottom"&gt;
       &lt;td width="64%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="5%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="1%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="5%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="1%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="5%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="1%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="5%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="1%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="5%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="1%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="5%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td width="1%"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr style="font-size: 8pt" valign="bottom"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="center" colspan="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accumulated&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr style="font-size: 8pt" valign="bottom"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="center" colspan="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Auction Rate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="center" colspan="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Other&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr style="font-size: 8pt" valign="bottom"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="center" colspan="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pension&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="center" colspan="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Securities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="center" colspan="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Comprehensive&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr style="font-size: 8pt" valign="bottom"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="center" colspan="2" style="border-bottom: 1px solid #000000"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adjustments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="center" colspan="2" style="border-bottom: 1px solid #000000"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adjustment&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="center" colspan="2" style="border-bottom: 1px solid #000000"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Loss&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;!-- End Table Head --&gt;
   &lt;!-- Begin Table Body --&gt;
   &lt;tr valign="bottom" style="background: #cceeff"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;
   &lt;div style="margin-left:15px; text-indent:-15px"&gt;Balance as of October&amp;#160;3, 2008
   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;$&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(268&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;$&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(912&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;$&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(1,180&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr valign="bottom"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;
   &lt;div style="margin-left:15px; text-indent:-15px"&gt;Pension adjustment
   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(200&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;&amp;#8212;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(200&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr style="font-size: 1px"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;
   &lt;div style="margin-left:15px; text-indent:-15px"&gt;&amp;#160;
   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" colspan="2" align="right" style="border-top: 1px solid #000000"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" colspan="2" align="right" style="border-top: 1px solid #000000"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" colspan="2" align="right" style="border-top: 1px solid #000000"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr valign="bottom" style="background: #cceeff"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;
   &lt;div style="margin-left:15px; text-indent:-15px"&gt;Balance as of October&amp;#160;2, 2009
   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;$&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(468&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;$&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(912&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;$&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(1,380&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr valign="bottom"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;
   &lt;div style="margin-left:15px; text-indent:-15px"&gt;Pension adjustment
   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;83&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;&amp;#8212;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;83&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr style="font-size: 1px"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;
   &lt;div style="margin-left:15px; text-indent:-15px"&gt;&amp;#160;
   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" colspan="2" align="right" style="border-top: 1px solid #000000"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" colspan="2" align="right" style="border-top: 1px solid #000000"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" colspan="2" align="right" style="border-top: 1px solid #000000"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr valign="bottom" style="background: #cceeff"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;
   &lt;div style="margin-left:15px; text-indent:-15px"&gt;Balance as of October&amp;#160;1, 2010
   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;$&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(385&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;$&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(912&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" align="left"&gt;$&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td align="right"&gt;(1,297&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td nowrap="nowrap"&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;tr style="font-size: 1px"&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;
   &lt;div style="margin-left:15px; text-indent:-15px"&gt;&amp;#160;
   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
           &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" colspan="2" align="right" style="border-top: 3px double #000000"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
           &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" colspan="2" align="right" style="border-top: 3px double #000000"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
           &lt;td nowrap="nowrap" colspan="2" align="right" style="border-top: 3px double #000000"&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
       &lt;td&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
   &lt;!-- End Table Body --&gt;
   &lt;/table&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;RECENTLY ISSUED ACCOUNTING PRONOUNCEMENTS&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ASC 810&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;In December&amp;#160;2007, the FASB issued amendments to ASC 810-&lt;i&gt;Consolidation &lt;/i&gt;(&amp;#8220;ASC 810&amp;#8221;). ASC 810 amends
   previously issued authoritative literature to amend accounting and reporting standards for the
   noncontrolling interest in a subsidiary and for the deconsolidation of a subsidiary. It also amends
   certain of consolidation procedures for consistency with the requirements of ASC 805. This
   statement is effective for fiscal years, and interim periods within those fiscal years, beginning
   on or after December&amp;#160;15, 2008. The statement was applied prospectively as of the beginning of the
   fiscal year. The adoption of ASC 810 did not have an impact on the Company&amp;#8217;s results of operations
   or financial position because the Company does not have any minority interests.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ASC 825&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;In February&amp;#160;2007, the FASB issued ASC 825-&lt;i&gt;Financial Instruments &lt;/i&gt;(&amp;#8220;ASC 825&amp;#8221;), including an
   amendment of ASC 320-&lt;i&gt;Investments-Debt and Equity Securities &lt;/i&gt;(&amp;#8220;ASC 320&amp;#8221;), which permits entities to
   choose to measure many financial instruments and certain other items at fair value that are not
   currently required to be measured at fair value. ASC 825 was effective for the Company beginning on
   October&amp;#160;3, 2009. The adoption of ASC 825 did not have a material impact on the Company&amp;#8217;s results
   from operations or financial position.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 12pt"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ASU 2009-13 and ASU 2009-14&lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div align="left" style="font-size: 10pt; margin-top: 6pt"&gt;In September&amp;#160;2009, the FASB reached a consensus on Accounting Standards Update
   (&amp;#8220;ASU&amp;#8221;)-2009-13-&lt;i&gt;Revenue Recognition (&amp;#8220;ASC 605&amp;#8221;) &amp;#8212; Multiple-Deliverable Revenue Arrangements &lt;/i&gt;(&amp;#8220;ASU
   2009-13&amp;#8221;) and ASU 2009-14- &lt;i&gt;Software (&amp;#8220;ASC 985&amp;#8221;) &amp;#8212; Certain Revenue Arrangements That Include
   Software Elements &lt;/i&gt;(&amp;#8220;ASU 2009-14&amp;#8221;). ASU 2009-13 modifies the requirements that must be met for an
   entity to recognize revenue from the sale of a delivered item that is part of a multiple-element
   arrangement when other items have not yet been delivered. ASU 2009-13 eliminates the requirement
   that all undelivered elements must have either: i) Vendor Specific Objective Evidence or VSOE or
   ii) third-party evidence, or TPE, before an entity can recognize the portion of an overall
   arrangement consideration that is attributable to items that already have been delivered. In the
   absence of VSOE or TPE of the standalone selling price for one or more delivered or undelivered
   elements in a multiple-element arrangement, entities will be required to estimate the selling
   prices of those elements. Overall arrangement consideration will be allocated to each element (both
   delivered and undelivered items) based on their relative selling prices, regardless of whether
   those selling prices are evidenced by VSOE or TPE or are based on the entity&amp;#8217;s estimated selling
   price. The residual method of allocating arrangement consideration has been eliminated. ASU 2009-14
   modifies the software revenue recognition guidance to exclude from its scope tangible products that
   contain both software and non-software components that function together to deliver a product&amp;#8217;s
   essential functionality. These new updates are effective for revenue arrangements entered into or
   materially modified in fiscal years beginning on or after June&amp;#160;15, 2010. The Company is currently
   evaluating the impact that the adoption of these ASUs will have on its consolidated financial
   statements.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
</NonNumbericText>
          <NonNumericTextHeader>&lt;!--DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd" --&gt;
   &lt;!-- Begin Block Tagged Note</NonNumericTextHeader>
          <FootnoteIndexer />
          <hasSegments>false</hasSegments>
          <hasScenarios>false</hasScenarios>
          <DisplayDateInUSFormat>false</DisplayDateInUSFormat>
        </Cell>
      </Cells>
      <OriginalInstanceReportColumns />
      <ElementDataType>us-types:textBlockItemType</ElementDataType>
      <SimpleDataType>textblock</SimpleDataType>
      <ElementDefenition>This element may be used to describe all significant accounting policies of the reporting entity.</ElementDefenition>
      <ElementReferences>Reference 1: http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/presentationRef
 -Publisher AICPA
 -Name Accounting Principles Board Opinion (APB)
 -Number 22
 -Paragraph 8

</ElementReferences>
      <IsTotalLabel>false</IsTotalLabel>
    </Row>
  </Rows>
  <Footnotes />
  <NumberOfCols>1</NumberOfCols>
  <NumberOfRows>2</NumberOfRows>
  <HasScenarios>false</HasScenarios>
  <MonetaryRoundingLevel>UnKnown</MonetaryRoundingLevel>
  <SharesRoundingLevel>UnKnown</SharesRoundingLevel>
  <PerShareRoundingLevel>UnKnown</PerShareRoundingLevel>
  <HasPureData>false</HasPureData>
  <SharesShouldBeRounded>true</SharesShouldBeRounded>
</InstanceReport>
</XBRL>
</TEXT>

</DOCUMENT>